[
    {
        "front": "じこ",
        "back": "accident",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶつかる",
        "back": "to crash; to bump into",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "だんせい",
        "back": "man",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "じょせい",
        "back": "woman",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいかん",
        "back": "policeman",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "せん",
        "back": "line",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひく",
        "back": "to draw",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "きゅうきゅうしゃ",
        "back": "ambulance",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "けが",
        "back": "injury",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばしょ",
        "back": "place",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "なくなる",
        "back": "to die",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "うんてんしゅ",
        "back": "driver",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    },
    {
        "front": "げんいん",
        "back": "cause",
        "chapter": "N4 C27"
    }
]